

# **PROFILE**

I'm a learning User Experience Designer, who loves building web, iPad & mobile solutions. I have designed features and flows for various products i.e., from requirement gathering to their prototyping. I also love designing digital media kits (brand websites, logos, banners, etc.) for both online and offline advertising.

And, I seek my creative inspiration from mother nature and use tools like Figma, Sketch, Marvel app, Zeplin, Adobe XD & Photoshop.

#### CONTACT

PHONE:

+91-9131991448

WEBSITE:

https://purvakushwaha.github.io

EMAIL:

purva.kushwaha99@gmail.com

DRIBBLE:

Purva\_Kushwaha

LINKEDLN:

purva-kushwaha-5885aa118

#### **HOBBIES**

Table Tennis Reading Travelling

# PURVA K KUSHWAHA

UX Designer

## **EDUCATION**

## Indore Institute of Science & Technology, Indore, MP

2015 - 2019

In my college days, I have coordinated and organized many events like **Techfest**. Technical events of **Microsoft**, **Facebook** and anchored at cultural events like Concerts, Annual Day, Kavi-Sammelan, etc.

- I was awarded as **Star Achiever** in my Final Year.
- I had won Madhya Pradesh **States**, Table Tennis, 2015.
- My research paper 'RNN Based Music Generation paper' got selected in **AICTE Conference**, Japan.
- My Minor project is BookFood Website, a website for user and caters and my Major project was Smart Dustbin with GPS service using IOT & Rasberry Pi.

# Atomic Energy Central School No.1, Tarapur, Dist. Palghar, MH

2002 - 2015

I was the **Head Girl** and twice severed as **House Caption**. Under my leadership, we had won many co-curricular activities (Debates, Quizzes, Paper presentation to Group Dance, Group Singing, etc.) and various indoor and outdoor team as well as individual events.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Freelancing - Independent Designer

June, 2020 – Present

These days, I am lucky to work with many small companies and startups and help them design their **Media Kits**, **Online/Offline marketing elements** from logos, browser, visiting and invitation cards to websites, mobile application screens.

# Paragon Business Solutions Pvt. Ltd. - UX Designer (Digivalet & CasaDigi)

May 2019 - June 2020

**Digivalet** is the world's first touch-based guest room experience solution whereas **CasaDigi** is for luxurious homes. I have experienced designing user interactive features like **Food & Beverages**, **Chatbot**, etc. and worked on many internal projects like revamping **Digivalet Dashboard**, **CasaDigi Studio**, etc.

# EngineerBabu Pvt. Ltd. - Graphic Designer Intern

March 2018 - July 2018

During my internship, I had experienced creating various **advertising elements** like Logos, hiring posters, t-shirts, cups, laptop stickers.

#### Indore Technical Community & Microsoft Student Partner

2017 - 2019

My passion for planning and designing products rose more after visiting BITs Pilani Summit, Rajasthan Hackathon 5.0 and joining communities like Google Developers Group, Facebook Developers Circle, GirlScript and Women Techmakers, Indore. I have also worked as Student Ambassador at Skillenza, Progate, Internshala (8.0, 9.0 and 12.0).

#### Other Internships

- Affimantus Technologies, Indore (Website Development)
- L&T Electrical & Automation, Indore (IOT & Product Development Phases)
- Nuclear Power Corporations of India Ltd. (TAPS) Setup of PPPoE Authentication Sever Development Phases